{
    "subject": "Al_Pacino",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "Looking_for_Richard",
    "human_readable": "Al Pacino acted in Looking for Richard.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.98052978515625,
            "question": "Was Al Pacino involved in the production of Looking for Richard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9459354877471924,
            "question": "Did Al Pacino receive any awards for his role in Looking for Richard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7940950393676758,
            "question": "Who starred in Looking for Richard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7774062156677246,
            "question": "Is Al Pacino known for his acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5409208536148071,
            "question": "What is the plot of Looking for Richard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5274898409843445,
            "question": "What kind of film is Looking for Richard?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4307610094547272,
            "question": "What movie did Al Pacino act in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.346060574054718,
            "question": "Has Al Pacino appeared in other notable films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32327479124069214,
            "question": "What year was Looking for Richard released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1652505099773407,
            "question": "Name a famous movie directed by Al Pacino."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Al Pacino acted in Looking for Richard.",
            "html": "yago_916_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Looking for Richard released?",
            "html": "yago_916_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Al Pacino appeared in other notable films?",
            "html": "yago_916_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What movie did Al Pacino act in?",
            "html": "yago_916_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_916_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_916_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_916_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_916_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_916_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_916_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_916_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_916_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_916_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_916_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Al Pacino acted in Looking for Richard.\" The texts mention Al Pacino's involvement as both an actor and a subject of the documentary, further supporting this claim."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}